var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "آدَمَ",
        "answer": "Adam",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِآدَمَ",
        "answer": "to Adam",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "liādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا آدَمُ",
        "answer": "O Adam",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yāādamu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا آدَمُ",
        "answer": "O Adam",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yāādamu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "آدَمُ",
        "answer": "And Adam disobeyed",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ādamu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْلِيسَ",
        "answer": "Iblis",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ib'līsa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبَىٰ",
        "answer": "and refused",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wa-abā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبَىٰ",
        "answer": "he refused",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "abā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَاكَ",
        "answer": "come to you",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "atāka",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "bring you",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "ātīkum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَاهَا",
        "answer": "he came to it",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "atāhā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأْتِيَاهُ",
        "answer": "So go to him",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "fatiyāhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَنَأْتِيَنَّكَ",
        "answer": "Then we will surely produce for you",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "falanatiyannaka",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَىٰ",
        "answer": "came",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "atā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "ائْتُوا",
        "answer": "come",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "i'tū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَىٰ",
        "answer": "he comes",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "atā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "yati",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِهِ",
        "answer": "comes to Him",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "yatihi",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "comes to you",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "yatiyannakum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَتْكَ",
        "answer": "came to you",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "atatka",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِينَا",
        "answer": "he brings us",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "yatīnā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "come to them",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "tatihim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيتَ",
        "answer": "you are granted",
        "pcklId": "424",
        "tlit": "ūtīta",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "We have given you",
        "pcklId": "425",
        "tlit": "ātaynāka",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) coming",
        "pcklId": "540",
        "tlit": "ātiyatun",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُؤْثِرَكَ",
        "answer": "we will prefer you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "nu'thiraka",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَثَرِي",
        "answer": "my tracks",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "atharī",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَثَرِ",
        "answer": "(the) track",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "athari",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَجَلٌ",
        "answer": "and a term",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wa-ajalun",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُذْهَا",
        "answer": "Seize it",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "khudh'hā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْخُذْهُ",
        "answer": "will take him",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "yakhudh'hu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْخُذْ",
        "answer": "seize (me)",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "takhudh",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "other",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "another",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "another time",
        "pcklId": "235",
        "tlit": "ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "another",
        "pcklId": "236",
        "tlit": "ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخِي",
        "answer": "my brother",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "akhī",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَخُوكَ",
        "answer": "and your brother",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "wa-akhūka",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْتُكَ",
        "answer": "your sister",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "ukh'tuka",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "آذَنَ",
        "answer": "I gave permission",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ādhana",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَذِنَ",
        "answer": "has given permission",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "adhina",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَآرِبُ",
        "answer": "(are) uses",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "maāribu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْضِنَا",
        "answer": "our land",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "arḍinā",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْضِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your land",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "arḍikum",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْرِي",
        "answer": "my strength",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "azrī",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(the) Children of Israel",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "O Children of Israel",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(the) Children of Israel",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسِفًا",
        "answer": "(and) sorrowful",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "asifan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُوا",
        "answer": "Eat",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "kulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُوا",
        "answer": "Eat",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "kulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَكَلَا",
        "answer": "Then they both ate",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "fa-akalā",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "(But)",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except (for)",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except (for)",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "744",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "The One Who",
        "pcklId": "745",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "746",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِي",
        "answer": "and the One Who",
        "pcklId": "747",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "that which",
        "pcklId": "748",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One",
        "pcklId": "749",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) your god",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "ilāhukum",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَٰهُ",
        "answer": "and the god",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "wa-ilāhu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهِكَ",
        "answer": "your god",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "ilāhika",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهُكُمُ",
        "answer": "your God",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "ilāhukumu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah ",
        "pcklId": "1755",
        "tlit": "al-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1756",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1757",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1758",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1759",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1760",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "381",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "382",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "383",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "384",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "385",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "to us",
        "pcklId": "386",
        "tlit": "ilaynā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to him",
        "pcklId": "387",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "388",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "389",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "to us",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "tlit": "ilaynā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "at",
        "pcklId": "393",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "394",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "395",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to him",
        "pcklId": "396",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "towards",
        "pcklId": "397",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "to us",
        "pcklId": "398",
        "tlit": "ilaynā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْتًا",
        "answer": "any curve",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "amtan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأْمُرْ",
        "answer": "And enjoin",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "wamur",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرِي",
        "answer": "my task",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "amrī",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرِي",
        "answer": "my task",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "amrī",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(in) their affair",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "amrahum",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرِي",
        "answer": "my order",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "amrī",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرِي",
        "answer": "my order",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "amrī",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمِّكَ",
        "answer": "your mother",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ummika",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمِّكَ",
        "answer": "your mother",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ummika",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا ابْنَ أُمَّ",
        "answer": "O son of my mother",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yabna-umma",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِمَّا",
        "answer": "Either",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "immā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِمَّا",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wa-immā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "339",
        "tlit": "yu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We believe",
        "pcklId": "340",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "You believe",
        "pcklId": "341",
        "tlit": "āmantum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "we believe",
        "pcklId": "342",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآمَنَ",
        "answer": "and believes",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "waāmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنْ",
        "answer": "believes",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "yu'min",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنًا",
        "answer": "(as) a believer",
        "pcklId": "754",
        "tlit": "mu'minan",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a believer",
        "pcklId": "755",
        "tlit": "mu'minun",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "آنَسْتُ",
        "answer": "[I] perceived",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ānastu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "آنَاءِ",
        "answer": "(the) hours",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ānāi",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَهْلِهِ",
        "answer": "to his family",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "li-ahlihi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِي",
        "answer": "my family",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "ahlī",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "ahli",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكَ",
        "answer": "(on) your family",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "ahlaka",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "the first",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُولَىٰ",
        "answer": "the former",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "l-ūlā",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُولَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) the former",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "l-ūlā",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُولَىٰ",
        "answer": "the former",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "l-ūlā",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأُولِي",
        "answer": "for possessors",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "li-ulī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأُولِي",
        "answer": "for possessors",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "li-ulī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةً",
        "answer": "(as) a sign",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "āyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "āyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِي",
        "answer": "with My Signs",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "biāyātī",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَةٍ",
        "answer": "with a Sign",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "biāyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآيَاتٍ",
        "answer": "surely (are) Signs",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "laāyātin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "āyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتُنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "āyātunā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "in (the) Signs",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "biāyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآيَاتٍ",
        "answer": "surely (are) Signs",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "laāyātin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَةٍ",
        "answer": "a sign",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "biāyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِكَ",
        "answer": "Your signs",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "āyātika",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَحْرِ",
        "answer": "the sea",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-baḥri",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَدَتْ",
        "answer": "so became apparent",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fabadat",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبْرَحَ",
        "answer": "we will cease",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "nabraḥa",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصُرْتُ",
        "answer": "I perceived",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "baṣur'tu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْصُرُوا",
        "answer": "they perceive",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yabṣurū",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "baṣīran",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "sight",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "baṣīran",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِكَ",
        "answer": "after you",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "baʿdika",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُكُمْ",
        "answer": "some of you",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "baʿḍukum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "to others",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "libaʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "and more lasting",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-abqā",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "and Ever Lasting",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wa-abqā",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "and more lasting",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-abqā",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "and more lasting",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-abqā",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "(that will) deteriorate",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yablā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا ابْنَ أُمَّ",
        "answer": "O son of my mother",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "yabna-umma",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children of Israel",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بَنِي",
        "answer": "O Children of Israel",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "yābanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children of Israel",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَالُ",
        "answer": "(is the) case",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bālu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْضَاءَ",
        "answer": "white",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "bayḍāa",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمَا",
        "answer": "(is) between them",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "baynahumā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَنَا",
        "answer": "between us",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "baynanā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَكَ",
        "answer": "and between you",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "wabaynaka",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "among them",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "among themselves",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(is) before them",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيِّنَاتِ",
        "answer": "the clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "tlit": "l-bayināti",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيِّنَةُ",
        "answer": "evidence",
        "pcklId": "360",
        "tlit": "bayyinatu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَتْبَعَهُمْ",
        "answer": "Then followed them",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "fa-atbaʿahum",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّبَعَ",
        "answer": "and follows",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "wa-ittabaʿa",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعَ",
        "answer": "follows",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿa",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاتَّبِعُونِي",
        "answer": "so follow me",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "fa-ittabiʿūnī",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعَنِ",
        "answer": "you follow me",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿani",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّبِعُونَ",
        "answer": "they will follow",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "yattabiʿūna",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعَ",
        "answer": "follows",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿa",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَتَّبِعَ",
        "answer": "so we (could) have followed",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "fanattabiʿa",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath them",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتَ",
        "answer": "(is) under",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "taḥta",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابَ",
        "answer": "repents",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "tāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَابَ",
        "answer": "and turned",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "fatāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَارَةً",
        "answer": "time",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tāratan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الثَّرَىٰ",
        "answer": "the soil",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-tharā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِبَالِ",
        "answer": "the mountains",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-jibāli",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "اجْتَبَاهُ",
        "answer": "chose him",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ij'tabāhu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُذُوعِ",
        "answer": "(the) trunks",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "judhūʿi",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُجْرِمًا",
        "answer": "(as) a criminal",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "muj'riman",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُجْرِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the criminals",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-muj'rimīna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flows",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتُجْزَىٰ",
        "answer": "that may be recompensed",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "lituj'zā",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِي",
        "answer": "We recompense",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "najzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءُ",
        "answer": "(is) the reward",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "jazāu",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَسَدًا",
        "answer": "body",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "jasadan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "And appoint",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "wa-ij'ʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "made",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "So make",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "fa-ij'ʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَمَعَ",
        "answer": "and put together",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fajamaʿa",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَجْمِعُوا",
        "answer": "So put together",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "fa-ajmiʿū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَانِبَ",
        "answer": "on (the) side",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "jāniba",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَاحِكَ",
        "answer": "your side",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "janāḥika",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِجُنُودِهِ",
        "answer": "with his forces",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bijunūdihi",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتُ",
        "answer": "Gardens",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "jannātu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "Paradise",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْهَرْ",
        "answer": "you speak aloud",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tajhar",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجُوعَ",
        "answer": "you will be hungry",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tajūʿa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِئْتَ",
        "answer": "you came",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "ji'ta",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِئْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "we came to you",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "ji'nāka",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجِئْتَنَا",
        "answer": "Have you come to us",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "aji'tanā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَنَا",
        "answer": "has come to us",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "jāanā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحَبَّةً",
        "answer": "love",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "maḥabbatan",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِبَالُهُمْ",
        "answer": "Their ropes",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ḥibāluhum",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْدِثُ",
        "answer": "it may cause",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'dithu",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَدِيثُ",
        "answer": "the narration",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ḥadīthu",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنُحَرِّقَنَّهُ",
        "answer": "Surely we will burn it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "lanuḥarriqannahu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْزَنَ",
        "answer": "she grieves",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "taḥzana",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنًا",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "ḥasanan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُسْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "the Most Beautiful",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "l-ḥus'nā",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْشَرَ",
        "answer": "will be assembled",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'shara",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَحْشُرُ",
        "answer": "and We will gather",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wanaḥshuru",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَحْشُرُهُ",
        "answer": "and We will gather him",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wanaḥshuruhu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَشَرْتَنِي",
        "answer": "You raised me",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ḥashartanī",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "the True",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحْلُلْ",
        "answer": "And untie",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-uḥ'lul",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَحِلَّ",
        "answer": "lest should descend",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fayaḥilla",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْلِلْ",
        "answer": "on whom descends",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yaḥlil",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحِلَّ",
        "answer": "descend",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yaḥilla",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِحَمْدِ",
        "answer": "with praise",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "biḥamdi",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْمِلُ",
        "answer": "will bear",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yaḥmilu",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمَلَ",
        "answer": "carried",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ḥamala",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُمِّلْنَا",
        "answer": "[we] were made to carry",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ḥummil'nā",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِمْلًا",
        "answer": "(as) a load",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ḥim'lan",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِيطُونَ",
        "answer": "they encompass",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yuḥīṭūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "wherever",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْيَىٰ",
        "answer": "live",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaḥyā",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْحَيِّ",
        "answer": "before the Ever-Living",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "lil'ḥayyi",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةَ",
        "answer": "life",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayata",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the life",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيَّةٌ",
        "answer": "(was) a snake",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "ḥayyatun",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْرُجْ",
        "answer": "it will come out",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "takhruj",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخْرَجْنَا",
        "answer": "then We (have) brought forth",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "fa-akhrajnā",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُخْرِجُكُمْ",
        "answer": "We will bring you out",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "nukh'rijukum",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتُخْرِجَنَا",
        "answer": "to drive us out",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "litukh'rijanā",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْرِجَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "they drive you out",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "yukh'rijākum",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخْرَجَ",
        "answer": "Then he brought forth",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "fa-akhraja",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْرِجَنَّكُمَا",
        "answer": "(let) him drive you both",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "yukh'rijannakumā",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَخْزَىٰ",
        "answer": "and disgraced",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wanakhzā",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخَشَعَتِ",
        "answer": "And (will be) humbled",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wakhashaʿati",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْشَىٰ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yakhshā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْشَىٰ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yakhshā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْشَىٰ",
        "answer": "being afraid",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "takhshā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَشِيتُ",
        "answer": "[I] feared",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "khashītu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْصِفَانِ",
        "answer": "(to) fasten",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yakhṣifāni",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَطَايَانَا",
        "answer": "our sins",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "khaṭāyānā",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَطْبُكَ",
        "answer": "(is) your case",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "khaṭbuka",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَخَافَتُونَ",
        "answer": "They are murmuring",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yatakhāfatūna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْفِيهَا",
        "answer": "[I] hide it",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ukh'fīhā",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَخْفَى",
        "answer": "and the more hidden",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wa-akhfā",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخُلْدِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Eternity",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-khul'di",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "abiding forever",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "Abiding forever",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاخْلَعْ",
        "answer": "so remove",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fa-ikh'laʿ",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُخْلِفُهُ",
        "answer": "we will fail it",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "nukh'lifuhu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخْلَفْتُمْ",
        "answer": "so you broke",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "fa-akhlaftum",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْلَفْنَا",
        "answer": "we broke",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "akhlafnā",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُخْلَفَهُ",
        "answer": "you will fail to (keep) it",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "tukh'lafahu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِلَافٍ",
        "answer": "opposite sides",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "khilāfin",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْفَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) behind them",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "khalfahum",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We created you",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "khalaqnākum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقَهُ",
        "answer": "its form",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "khalqahu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُوَارٌ",
        "answer": "a lowing sound",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "khuwārun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخَفْ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "takhaf",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَخَافُ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "nakhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخَافَا",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "takhāfā",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخَفْ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "takhaf",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخَافُ",
        "answer": "fearing",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "takhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخَافُ",
        "answer": "he will fear",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yakhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِيفَةً",
        "answer": "a fear",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "khīfatan",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَابَ",
        "answer": "he failed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "khāba",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَابَ",
        "answer": "will have failed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khāba",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "اخْتَرْتُكَ",
        "answer": "(have) chosen you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ikh'tartuka",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Best",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخَيَّلُ",
        "answer": "seemed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yukhayyalu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّرَجَاتُ",
        "answer": "(will be) the ranks",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-darajātu",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَرَكًا",
        "answer": "to be overtaken",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "darakan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّاعِيَ",
        "answer": "the caller",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "l-dāʿiya",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدُلُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "I show you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "adullukum",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدُلُّكَ",
        "answer": "I direct you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "adulluka",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَذْكُرَكَ",
        "answer": "And [we] remember You",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "wanadhkuraka",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَذَكَّرُ",
        "answer": "may take heed",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "yatadhakkaru",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِذِكْرِي",
        "answer": "for My remembrance",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "lidhik'rī",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرِي",
        "answer": "My remembrance",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "dhik'rī",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرًا",
        "answer": "a Reminder",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "dhik'ran",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرًا",
        "answer": "remembrance",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "dhik'ran",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرِي",
        "answer": "My remembrance",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "dhik'rī",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذْكِرَةً",
        "answer": "(as) a reminder",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "tadhkiratan",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِلَّ",
        "answer": "we were humiliated",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nadhilla",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "اذْهَبْ",
        "answer": "Go",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "idh'hab",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "اذْهَبْ",
        "answer": "Go",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "idh'hab",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اذْهَبَا",
        "answer": "Go, both of you",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "idh'habā",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَذْهَبَا",
        "answer": "and do away",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wayadhhabā",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاذْهَبْ",
        "answer": "Then go",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "fa-idh'hab",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَأْسِي",
        "answer": "by my head",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "birasī",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَىٰ",
        "answer": "he saw",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "raā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "and I see",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "wa-arā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْنَ",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "yarawna",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَيْتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "you saw them",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "ra-aytahum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "you will see",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنُرِيَكَ",
        "answer": "That We may show you",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "linuriyaka",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We showed him",
        "pcklId": "291",
        "tlit": "araynāhu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "479",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "480",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "481",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "482",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "483",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمَا",
        "answer": "(is) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "484",
        "tlit": "rabbukumā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "485",
        "tlit": "rabbunā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "486",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "487",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّ",
        "answer": "in (the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "488",
        "tlit": "birabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "in our Lord",
        "pcklId": "489",
        "tlit": "birabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُ",
        "answer": "(to) his Lord",
        "pcklId": "490",
        "tlit": "rabbahu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "491",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "492",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "493",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكُمُ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "494",
        "tlit": "rabbakumu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "495",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "496",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "497",
        "tlit": "rabbahu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "498",
        "tlit": "rabbuhu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "499",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) his Lord",
        "pcklId": "500",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "501",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "502",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "503",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "504",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "505",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَرَبَّصُوا",
        "answer": "so await",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fatarabbaṣū",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَرَبِّصٌ",
        "answer": "(is) waiting",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "mutarabbiṣun",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَجَعْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "So We returned you",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "farajaʿnāka",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَجَعَ",
        "answer": "Then Musa returned",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "farajaʿa",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجِعُ",
        "answer": "it (could) return",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yarjiʿu",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجِعَ",
        "answer": "returns",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "yarjiʿa",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرْجُلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your feet",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "wa-arjulakum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلرَّحْمَٰنِ",
        "answer": "for the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "lilrraḥmāni",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "The Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "al-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَرْدَىٰ",
        "answer": "lest you perish",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fatardā",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We have provided you",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "razaqnākum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَرْزُقُكَ",
        "answer": "provide (for) you",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "narzuquka",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرِزْقُ",
        "answer": "And (the) provision",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "wariz'qu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقًا",
        "answer": "(for) provision",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "riz'qan",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَرْسِلْ",
        "answer": "so send",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "fa-arsil",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْتَ",
        "answer": "You sent",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "arsalta",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولَا",
        "answer": "both (are) Messengers",
        "pcklId": "317",
        "tlit": "rasūlā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "l-rasūli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "319",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَرْضَىٰ",
        "answer": "that You be pleased",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "litarḍā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَضِيَ",
        "answer": "and He has accepted",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "waraḍiya",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْضَىٰ",
        "answer": "be satisfied",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "tarḍā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَارْعَوْا",
        "answer": "and pasture",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-ir'ʿaw",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْقُبْ",
        "answer": "you respect",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tarqub",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدَانِ",
        "answer": "they intend",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "yurīdāni",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَدْتُمْ",
        "answer": "did you desire",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "aradttum",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "زُرْقًا",
        "answer": "blue-eyed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "zur'qan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَزَكَّىٰ",
        "answer": "purifies himself",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "tazakkā",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَهْرَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) splendor",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "zahrata",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجًا",
        "answer": "pairs",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "azwājan",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِزَوْجِكَ",
        "answer": "and to your wife",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "walizawjika",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجًا",
        "answer": "pairs",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "azwājan",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "زِدْنِي",
        "answer": "Increase me",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "zid'nī",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزِّينَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the festival",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-zīnati",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "زِينَةِ",
        "answer": "ornaments",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "zīnati",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "And they ask you",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "wayasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسْأَلُكَ",
        "answer": "We ask you",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "nasaluka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُؤْلَكَ",
        "answer": "your request",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "su'laka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُسَبِّحَكَ",
        "answer": "we may glorify You",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "nusabbiḥaka",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَبِّحْ",
        "answer": "and glorify",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wasabbiḥ",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَبِّحْ",
        "answer": "and glorify",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "fasabbiḥ",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبَقَ",
        "answer": "has preceded",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "sabaqa",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبَقَتْ",
        "answer": "(that) preceded",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "sabaqat",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبُلًا",
        "answer": "ways",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "subulan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْجُدُوا",
        "answer": "Prostrate",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "us'judū",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَجَدُوا",
        "answer": "then they prostrated",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "fasajadū",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُجَّدًا",
        "answer": "prostrating",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "sujjadan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُسْحِتَكُمْ",
        "answer": "lest He will destroy you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fayus'ḥitakum",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسِحْرِكَ",
        "answer": "with your magic",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "bisiḥ'rika",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسِحْرٍ",
        "answer": "magic",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "bisiḥ'rin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسِحْرِهِمَا",
        "answer": "with their magic",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "bisiḥ'rihimā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِحْرِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their magic",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "siḥ'rihim",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "السِّحْرَ",
        "answer": "the magic",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-siḥ'ra",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "السِّحْرِ",
        "answer": "the magic",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-siḥ'ri",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَسَاحِرَانِ",
        "answer": "[two] magicians",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "lasāḥirāni",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاحِرٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a magician",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "sāḥirin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاحِرُ",
        "answer": "the magician",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-sāḥiru",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّحَرَةُ",
        "answer": "the magicians",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-saḥaratu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالسَّاحِلِ",
        "answer": "on the bank",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bil-sāḥili",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَسَرُّوا",
        "answer": "and they kept secret",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wa-asarrū",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "السِّرَّ",
        "answer": "the secret",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-sira",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْرَفَ",
        "answer": "transgresses",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "asrafa",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْرِ",
        "answer": "Travel by night",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "asri",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْعَىٰ",
        "answer": "it strives",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tasʿā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْعَىٰ",
        "answer": "moving swiftly",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tasʿā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْعَىٰ",
        "answer": "(were) moving",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "tasʿā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَاكِنِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their dwellings",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "masākinihim",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَلَكَ",
        "answer": "and inserted",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wasalaka",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّلَامُ",
        "answer": "And peace",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "wal-salāmu",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّلْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the quails",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-salwā",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّامِرِيُّ",
        "answer": "the Samiri",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-sāmiriyu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّامِرِيُّ",
        "answer": "the Samiri",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-sāmiriyu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا سَامِرِيُّ",
        "answer": "O Samiri",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yāsāmiriyyu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْمَعُ",
        "answer": "I hear",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "asmaʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْمَعُ",
        "answer": "you will hear",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "tasmaʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَمِعْ",
        "answer": "so listen",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tamiʿ",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَسْمَاءُ",
        "answer": "the Names",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-asmāu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "and the heavens",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "wal-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسَمًّى",
        "answer": "determined",
        "pcklId": "379",
        "tlit": "musamman",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(some) years",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "sinīna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَاءَ",
        "answer": "and evil",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wasāa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُوءٍ",
        "answer": "disease",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "sūin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوْآتُهُمَا",
        "answer": "their shame",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "sawātuhumā",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاعَةَ",
        "answer": "the Hour",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-sāʿata",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوَّلَتْ",
        "answer": "suggested",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "sawwalat",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَوَىٰ",
        "answer": "is established",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "is'tawā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّوِيِّ",
        "answer": "[the] even",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-sawiyi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُوًى",
        "answer": "even",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "suwan",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِيرَتَهَا",
        "answer": "(to) its state",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "sīratahā",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَتَّىٰ",
        "answer": "diverse",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "shattā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَجَرَةِ",
        "answer": "(the) tree",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "shajarati",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْدُدْ",
        "answer": "Reinforce",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ush'dud",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "(is) more severe",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "(is) more severe",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْرَحْ",
        "answer": "Expand",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ish'raḥ",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَشْرِكْهُ",
        "answer": "And make him share",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "wa-ashrik'hu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّفَاعَةُ",
        "answer": "the intercession",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-shafāʿatu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَشْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "that you be distressed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "litashqā",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَشْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "so (that) you would suffer",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fatashqā",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "suffer",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yashqā",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّمْسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the sun",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-shamsi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "things",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاصْبِرْ",
        "answer": "So be patient",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "fa-iṣ'bir",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاصْطَبِرْ",
        "answer": "and be steadfast",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "wa-iṣ'ṭabir",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّحُفِ",
        "answer": "the Scriptures",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ṣuḥufi",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصُدَّنَّكَ",
        "answer": "(let) avert you",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yaṣuddannaka",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدْرِي",
        "answer": "my breast",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ṣadrī",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصِّرَاطِ",
        "answer": "(of) the way",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "l-ṣirāṭi",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَرَّفْنَا",
        "answer": "and We have explained",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "waṣarrafnā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَفْصَفًا",
        "answer": "plain",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ṣafṣafan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَفًّا",
        "answer": "(in) a line",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṣaffan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَأُصَلِّبَنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "and surely I will crucify you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wala-uṣallibannakum",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "righteous (deeds)",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "the righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "the righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالصَّلَاةِ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "bil-ṣalati",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِتُصْنَعَ",
        "answer": "and that you may be brought up",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "walituṣ'naʿa",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَنَعُوا",
        "answer": "they have made",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ṣanaʿū",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَنَعُوا",
        "answer": "they (have) made",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ṣanaʿū",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاصْطَنَعْتُكَ",
        "answer": "And I (have) chosen you",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-iṣ'ṭanaʿtuka",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَصْوَاتُ",
        "answer": "the voices",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-aṣwātu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّورِ",
        "answer": "the Trumpet",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-ṣūri",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَضْحَىٰ",
        "answer": "exposed to the sun s heat",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taḍḥā",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضُحًى",
        "answer": "(at) forenoon",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ḍuḥan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاضْرِبْ",
        "answer": "and strike",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "fa-iḍ'rib",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرًّا",
        "answer": "any harm",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "ḍarran",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضِلُّ",
        "answer": "errs",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yaḍillu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلُّوا",
        "answer": "going astray",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ḍallū",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضِلُّ",
        "answer": "he will go astray",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yaḍillu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَضَلَّ",
        "answer": "And led astray",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "wa-aḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَضَلَّهُمُ",
        "answer": "and has led them astray",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "wa-aḍallahumu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاضْمُمْ",
        "answer": "And draw near",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-uḍ'mum",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَنْكًا",
        "answer": "straitened",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḍankan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَطْرَافَ",
        "answer": "(at the) ends",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wa-aṭrāfa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَرِيقًا",
        "answer": "a path",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṭarīqan",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِطَرِيقَتِكُمُ",
        "answer": "with your way",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "biṭarīqatikumu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَرِيقَةً",
        "answer": "(in) conduct",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ṭarīqatan",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَغَىٰ",
        "answer": "(has) transgressed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ṭaghā",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَغَىٰ",
        "answer": "(has) transgressed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṭaghā",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطْغَىٰ",
        "answer": "he will transgress",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaṭghā",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَطْغَوْا",
        "answer": "transgress",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "taṭghaw",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطَفِقَا",
        "answer": "and they began",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waṭafiqā",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "طُلُوعِ",
        "answer": "(the) rising",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ṭulūʿi",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطُّورِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Mount",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-ṭūri",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَطِيعُوا",
        "answer": "and obey",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wa-aṭīʿū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَطَالَ",
        "answer": "Then, did seem long",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "afaṭāla",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "طُوًى",
        "answer": "(of) Tuwa",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ṭuwan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيِّبَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) good things",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ṭayyibāti",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلْتَ",
        "answer": "you have remained",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ẓalta",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلْمًا",
        "answer": "wrongdoing",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "ẓul'man",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلْمًا",
        "answer": "injustice",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "ẓul'man",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَظْمَأُ",
        "answer": "will suffer from thirst",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taẓma-u",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْبُدْنِي",
        "answer": "so worship Me",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "fa-uʿ'bud'nī",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعِبَادِي",
        "answer": "with My slaves",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "biʿibādī",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَجِلْتُ",
        "answer": "and I hastened",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "waʿajil'tu",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْجَلْ",
        "answer": "hasten",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "taʿjal",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْجَلَكَ",
        "answer": "made you hasten",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "aʿjalaka",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِجْلًا",
        "answer": "a calf s",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ʿij'lan",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "an enemy",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "and an enemy",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "waʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your enemy",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwikum",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) an enemy",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "(as) enemy",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُعَذِّبْهُمْ",
        "answer": "torment them",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "tuʿadhib'hum",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابَ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "with a punishment",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "biʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "(in) punishment",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "And surely (the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "walaʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "with a punishment",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "biʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرَبِيًّا",
        "answer": "(in) Arabic",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ʿarabiyyan",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَرْشِ",
        "answer": "the Throne",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-ʿarshi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْرَضَ",
        "answer": "turns away",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "aʿraḍa",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْرَضَ",
        "answer": "turns away",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "aʿraḍa",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "you will be unclothed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taʿrā",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزْمًا",
        "answer": "determination",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ʿazman",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَشْرًا",
        "answer": "ten",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ʿashran",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَصَايَ",
        "answer": "(is) my staff",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ʿaṣāya",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِصِيُّهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their staffs",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "waʿiṣiyyuhum",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَعَصَيْتَ",
        "answer": "Then, have you disobeyed",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "afaʿaṣayta",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَصَىٰ",
        "answer": "And Adam disobeyed",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "waʿaṣā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْطَىٰ",
        "answer": "gave",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "aʿṭā",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعَاقِبَةُ",
        "answer": "and the outcome",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿāqibatu",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُقْدَةً",
        "answer": "(the) knot",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ʿuq'datan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاكِفِينَ",
        "answer": "being devoted to it",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ʿākifīna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاكِفًا",
        "answer": "devoted",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ʿākifan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَتَعْلَمُنَّ",
        "answer": "and surely you will know",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "walataʿlamunna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "He knows",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَتَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "Then you will know",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "fasataʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَّمَكُمُ",
        "answer": "taught you",
        "pcklId": "411",
        "tlit": "ʿallamakumu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "know best",
        "pcklId": "443",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمُهَا",
        "answer": "Its knowledge",
        "pcklId": "601",
        "tlit": "ʿil'muhā",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمًا",
        "answer": "(in) knowledge",
        "pcklId": "602",
        "tlit": "ʿil'man",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمًا",
        "answer": "(in) knowledge",
        "pcklId": "603",
        "tlit": "ʿil'man",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمًا",
        "answer": "(in) knowledge",
        "pcklId": "604",
        "tlit": "ʿil'man",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَعَالَى",
        "answer": "So high (above all)",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fataʿālā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَعْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "overcomes",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "is'taʿlā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "(will be) superior",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-aʿlā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعُلَى",
        "answer": "[the] high",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-ʿulā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعُلَىٰ",
        "answer": "[the] high",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "l-ʿulā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِلَ",
        "answer": "he has done",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "ʿamila",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلَ",
        "answer": "and does",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "waʿamila",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلْ",
        "answer": "does",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "yaʿmal",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَىٰ",
        "answer": "blind",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "aʿmā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَىٰ",
        "answer": "blind",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "aʿmā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(is) with",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَنَتِ",
        "answer": "And (will be) humbled",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waʿanati",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَهِدْنَا",
        "answer": "We made a covenant",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ʿahid'nā",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَهْدُ",
        "answer": "the promise",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-ʿahdu",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِوَجًا",
        "answer": "any crookedness",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ʿiwajan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِوَجَ",
        "answer": "deviation",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ʿiwaja",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنُعِيدُهَا",
        "answer": "We will return it",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "sanuʿīduhā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُعِيدُكُمْ",
        "answer": "We will return you",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "nuʿīdukum",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعِيشَةً",
        "answer": "(is) a life",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "maʿīshatan",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَيْنِي",
        "answer": "My eye",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ʿaynī",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَيْنُهَا",
        "answer": "her eyes",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ʿaynuhā",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَيْنَيْكَ",
        "answer": "your eyes",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ʿaynayka",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُرُوبِهَا",
        "answer": "its setting",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ghurūbihā",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَغَشِيَهُمْ",
        "answer": "but covered them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "faghashiyahum",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَشِيَهُمْ",
        "answer": "covered them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ghashiyahum",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَضَبِي",
        "answer": "My Anger",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ghaḍabī",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَضَبِي",
        "answer": "My Anger",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ghaḍabī",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَضَبٌ",
        "answer": "(the) Anger",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ghaḍabun",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَضْبَانَ",
        "answer": "angry",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ghaḍbāna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَغْفِرَ",
        "answer": "that He may forgive",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "liyaghfira",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَغَفَّارٌ",
        "answer": "the Perpetual Forgiver",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "laghaffārun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَمِّ",
        "answer": "the distress",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-ghami",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَنَمِي",
        "answer": "my sheep",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ghanamī",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَغَوَىٰ",
        "answer": "and erred",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faghawā",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without any",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "ghayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَتَنَّاكَ",
        "answer": "and We tried you",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wafatannāka",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَنَّا",
        "answer": "We (have) tried",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fatannā",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُتِنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are being tested",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "futintum",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَفْتِنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "that We may test them",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "linaftinahum",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُتُونًا",
        "answer": "(with) a trial",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "futūnan",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْرُطَ",
        "answer": "he will hasten",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yafruṭa",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَّقْتَ",
        "answer": "You caused division",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "farraqta",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْتَرُوا",
        "answer": "invent",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "taftarū",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "invented",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "if'tarā",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَطَرَنَا",
        "answer": "created us",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "faṭaranā",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْقَهُوا",
        "answer": "That they may understand",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yafqahū",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفْلَحَ",
        "answer": "(will be) successful",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "aflaḥa",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُفْلِحُ",
        "answer": "will be successful",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yuf'liḥu",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقَبَسٍ",
        "answer": "a burning brand",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "biqabasin",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَبَضْتُ",
        "answer": "so I took",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "faqabaḍtu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْضَةً",
        "answer": "a handful",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "qabḍatan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "qabli",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِ",
        "answer": "before him",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "qablihi",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "qabli",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "qabla",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "qablahum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "qabla",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَبْلَ",
        "answer": "and before",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "waqabla",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَتَلْتَ",
        "answer": "And you killed",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "waqatalta",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَرٍ",
        "answer": "the decreed (time)",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "qadarin",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُقَدَّسِ",
        "answer": "the sacred",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-muqadasi",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "اقْذِفِيهِ",
        "answer": "cast him",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "iq'dhifīhi",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاقْذِفِيهِ",
        "answer": "then cast it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-iq'dhifīhi",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَذَفْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "so we threw them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "faqadhafnāhā",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنَ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْآنًا",
        "answer": "(the) Quran",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "qur'ānan",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْقُرْآنِ",
        "answer": "with the Quran",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "bil-qur'āni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقَرَّ",
        "answer": "may be cooled",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taqarra",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرُونِ",
        "answer": "(of) the generations",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-qurūni",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرُونِ",
        "answer": "the generations",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-qurūni",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَقُصُّ",
        "answer": "We relate",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "naquṣṣu",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاقْضِ",
        "answer": "So decree",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "fa-iq'ḍi",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْضِي",
        "answer": "you can decree",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "taqḍī",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقْضَىٰ",
        "answer": "is completed",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "yuq'ḍā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاضٍ",
        "answer": "(are) decreeing",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "qāḍin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَأُقَطِّعَنَّ",
        "answer": "So surely I will cut off",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "fala-uqaṭṭiʿanna",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاعًا",
        "answer": "a level",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "qāʿan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "then he said",
        "pcklId": "901",
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "902",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "903",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "904",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "905",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "906",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَقُولُ",
        "answer": "and she said",
        "pcklId": "907",
        "tlit": "fataqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُولَا",
        "answer": "And speak",
        "pcklId": "908",
        "tlit": "faqūlā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "909",
        "tlit": "qālā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "910",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُولَا",
        "answer": "and say",
        "pcklId": "911",
        "tlit": "faqūlā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "912",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "913",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "914",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "915",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "916",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "917",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "918",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "919",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "920",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "921",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْنَا",
        "answer": "We said",
        "pcklId": "922",
        "tlit": "qul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "923",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "924",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "925",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "926",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "927",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "928",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "929",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and they said",
        "pcklId": "930",
        "tlit": "faqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "(had) said",
        "pcklId": "931",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "932",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "933",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "934",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولَ",
        "answer": "you would say",
        "pcklId": "935",
        "tlit": "taqūla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "936",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "937",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "938",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولَ",
        "answer": "you will say",
        "pcklId": "939",
        "tlit": "taqūla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "they will say",
        "pcklId": "940",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "will say",
        "pcklId": "941",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْ",
        "answer": "so say",
        "pcklId": "942",
        "tlit": "faqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلْ",
        "answer": "and say",
        "pcklId": "943",
        "tlit": "waqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْنَا",
        "answer": "We said",
        "pcklId": "944",
        "tlit": "qul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْنَا",
        "answer": "Then We said",
        "pcklId": "945",
        "tlit": "faqul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "946",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "947",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He will say",
        "pcklId": "948",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He will say",
        "pcklId": "949",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "950",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "951",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "surely they (would) have said",
        "pcklId": "952",
        "tlit": "laqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "953",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْقَوْلِ",
        "answer": "the word",
        "pcklId": "1664",
        "tlit": "bil-qawli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلِي",
        "answer": "my speech",
        "pcklId": "1665",
        "tlit": "qawlī",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلًا",
        "answer": "a word",
        "pcklId": "1666",
        "tlit": "qawlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلًا",
        "answer": "a word",
        "pcklId": "1667",
        "tlit": "qawlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلِي",
        "answer": "my word",
        "pcklId": "1668",
        "tlit": "qawlī",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلًا",
        "answer": "a word",
        "pcklId": "1669",
        "tlit": "qawlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقِمِ",
        "answer": "and establish",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "wa-aqimi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمَهُ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "qawmahu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِكَ",
        "answer": "your people",
        "pcklId": "323",
        "tlit": "qawmika",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمَكَ",
        "answer": "your people",
        "pcklId": "324",
        "tlit": "qawmaka",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "325",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "327",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "328",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "524",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "525",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "526",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَيُّومِ",
        "answer": "the Self-Subsisting",
        "pcklId": "568",
        "tlit": "l-qayūmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُبْرَى",
        "answer": "the Greatest",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "l-kub'rā",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكَبِيرُكُمُ",
        "answer": "(is) your chief",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "lakabīrukumu",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٍ",
        "answer": "a Record",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "kitābin",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "much",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "much",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "denies",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "but he denied",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "fakadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذِبًا",
        "answer": "a lie",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "kadhiban",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْرَهْتَنَا",
        "answer": "you compelled us",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "akrahtanā",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُلُهُ",
        "answer": "will nurse and rear him",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yakfuluhu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "(to) every",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّهَا",
        "answer": "all of them",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "kullahā",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلٌّ",
        "answer": "Each",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "kullun",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَةٌ",
        "answer": "(for) a Word",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "kalimatun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكَادُ",
        "answer": "I almost",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "akādu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "You are",
        "pcklId": "744",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكُونَ",
        "answer": "we will be",
        "pcklId": "745",
        "tlit": "nakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُ",
        "answer": "I had",
        "pcklId": "746",
        "tlit": "kuntu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكَانَ",
        "answer": "surely (would) have been",
        "pcklId": "747",
        "tlit": "lakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَانًا",
        "answer": "(in) a place",
        "pcklId": "1371",
        "tlit": "makānan",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْدَهُ",
        "answer": "his plan",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "kaydahu",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْدَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your plan",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "kaydakum",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْدُ",
        "answer": "a trick",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "kaydu",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَبِثْتَ",
        "answer": "Then you remained",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "falabith'ta",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبِثْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you remained",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "labith'tum",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبِثْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you remained",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "labith'tum",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِلِحْيَتِي",
        "answer": "by my beard",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "biliḥ'yatī",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَدُنَّا",
        "answer": "Us",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ladunnā",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِزَامًا",
        "answer": "an obligation",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "lizāman",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِسَانِي",
        "answer": "my tongue",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "lisānī",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَلْقَفْ",
        "answer": "it will swallow up",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "talqaf",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْقِهَا",
        "answer": "Throw it down",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "alqihā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَلْقَاهَا",
        "answer": "So he threw it down",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "fa-alqāhā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيُلْقِهِ",
        "answer": "then let cast it",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "falyul'qihi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَلْقَيْتُ",
        "answer": "And I cast",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "wa-alqaytu",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُلْقِيَ",
        "answer": "you throw",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "tul'qiya",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "throws",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "alqā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْقُوا",
        "answer": "you throw",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "alqū",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَلْقِ",
        "answer": "And throw",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "wa-alqi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأُلْقِيَ",
        "answer": "So were thrown down",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "fa-ul'qiya",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْقَى",
        "answer": "threw",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "alqā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "(of) the night",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيِّنًا",
        "answer": "gentle",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "layyinan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَّعْنَا",
        "answer": "We have given for enjoyment",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "mattaʿnā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْثَلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(the) best of them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "amthaluhum",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلِهِ",
        "answer": "like it",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "mith'lihi",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُثْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "the exemplary",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "l-muth'lā",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمُدَّنَّ",
        "answer": "extend",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "tamuddanna",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّةً",
        "answer": "another time",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "marratan",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِسَاسَ",
        "answer": "touch",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "misāsa",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمْشِي",
        "answer": "was going",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tamshī",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْشُونَ",
        "answer": "(as) they walk",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yamshūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "امْكُثُوا",
        "answer": "Stay here",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "um'kuthū",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْلِكُ",
        "answer": "possess",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yamliku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَلْكِنَا",
        "answer": "by our will",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "bimalkinā",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُلْكٍ",
        "answer": "and a kingdom",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "wamul'kin",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلِكُ",
        "answer": "the King",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "l-maliku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمَلَائِكَةِ",
        "answer": "to the Angels",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "lil'malāikati",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَعَكَ",
        "answer": "prevented you",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "manaʿaka",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَنَّا",
        "answer": "We conferred a favor",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "manannā",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَنَّ",
        "answer": "the Manna",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-mana",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَهْدًا",
        "answer": "(as) a bed",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "mahdan",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمُوتُ",
        "answer": "he will die",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yamūtu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءً",
        "answer": "water",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "māan",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْبَاءِ",
        "answer": "(the) news",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "anbāi",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَاتٍ",
        "answer": "plants",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "nabātin",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَبَذْتُهَا",
        "answer": "then threw it",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fanabadhtuhā",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَجَّيْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "but We saved you",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "fanajjaynāka",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْجَيْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We delivered you",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "anjaynākum",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّجْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "the private conversation",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-najwā",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّخْلِ",
        "answer": "(of) date-palms",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-nakhli",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُودِيَ",
        "answer": "he was called",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "nūdiya",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَنَازَعُوا",
        "answer": "Then they disputed",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "fatanāzaʿū",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَزَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We sent down",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "wanazzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We (have) sent down",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "and sent down",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "wa-anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We have sent it down",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "anzalnāhu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْزِيلًا",
        "answer": "A revelation",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "tanzīlan",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَنْسِفَنَّهُ",
        "answer": "certainly we will scatter it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "lanansifannahu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْسِفُهَا",
        "answer": "Will blast them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yansifuhā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسْفًا",
        "answer": "(in) particles",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nasfan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسْفًا",
        "answer": "(into) particles",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nasfan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْسَى",
        "answer": "forgets",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yansā",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَسِيَ",
        "answer": "but he forgot",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "fanasiya",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَسِيَ",
        "answer": "but he forgot",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "fanasiya",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَسِيتَهَا",
        "answer": "but you forgot them",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "fanasītahā",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْسَىٰ",
        "answer": "you will be forgotten",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "tunsā",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَانْظُرْ",
        "answer": "And look",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "wa-unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعْلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "your shoes",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "naʿlayka",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْعَامَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your cattle",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "anʿāmakum",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفَخُ",
        "answer": "will be blown",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yunfakhu",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "soul",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسًا",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "nafsan",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَفْسِي",
        "answer": "for Myself",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "linafsī",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "himself",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "nafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِي",
        "answer": "my soul",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "nafsī",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْفَعُ",
        "answer": "will benefit",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "tanfaʿu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْعًا",
        "answer": "any benefit",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "nafʿan",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the day",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-nahāri",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّهَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) intelligence",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "l-nuhā",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّهَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) intelligence",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "l-nuhā",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارًا",
        "answer": "a fire",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "nāran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارًا",
        "answer": "a fire",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "nāran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the fire",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْبِطَا",
        "answer": "Go down",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ih'biṭā",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَىٰ",
        "answer": "He guided (it)",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "hadā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَىٰ",
        "answer": "guide them",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "hadā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهَدَىٰ",
        "answer": "and guided (him)",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "wahadā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِ",
        "answer": "it guided",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "yahdi",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْتَدَىٰ",
        "answer": "remains guided",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "ih'tadā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْتَدَىٰ",
        "answer": "is guided",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "ih'tadā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "guidance",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "the Guidance",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "l-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "guidance",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدَايَ",
        "answer": "My guidance",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "hudāya",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهُشُّ",
        "answer": "and I bring down leaves",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-ahushu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَضْمًا",
        "answer": "deprivation",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "haḍman",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكْنَا",
        "answer": "We (have) destroyed",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ahlaknā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "(had) destroyed them",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ahlaknāhum",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَمْسًا",
        "answer": "a faint sound",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "hamsan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَوَىٰ",
        "answer": "he (has) perished",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "hawā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَوَاهُ",
        "answer": "his desires",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "hawāhu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجِدُ",
        "answer": "I find",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "ajidu",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجِدْ",
        "answer": "We found",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "najid",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَوْجَسَ",
        "answer": "So sensed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-awjasa",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوُجُوهُ",
        "answer": "the faces",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "l-wujūhu",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوحَىٰ",
        "answer": "is revealed",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yūḥā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْحَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We inspired",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "awḥaynā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوحَىٰ",
        "answer": "is inspired",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yūḥā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوحِيَ",
        "answer": "it has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ūḥiya",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْحَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We inspired",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "awḥaynā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحْيُهُ",
        "answer": "its revelation",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "waḥyuhu",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْوَادِ",
        "answer": "(are) in the valley",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "bil-wādi",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَذَرُهَا",
        "answer": "Then He will leave it",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "fayadharuhā",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَقِ",
        "answer": "(the) leaves",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waraqi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْزَارًا",
        "answer": "burdens",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "awzāran",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وِزْرًا",
        "answer": "a burden",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wiz'ran",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزِيرًا",
        "answer": "a minister",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wazīran",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسِعَ",
        "answer": "He has encompassed",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wasiʿa",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوَسْوَسَ",
        "answer": "Then whispered",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fawaswasa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعِدْكُمْ",
        "answer": "promise you",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yaʿid'kum",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوَاعَدْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "and We made a covenant with you",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "wawāʿadnākum",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْعِدًا",
        "answer": "an appointment",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "mawʿidan",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْعِدُكُمْ",
        "answer": "Your appointment",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "mawʿidukum",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْعِدِي",
        "answer": "(the) promise to me",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "mawʿidī",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْعِدَكَ",
        "answer": "promise to you",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "mawʿidaka",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْعِدًا",
        "answer": "(is) an appointment",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "mawʿidan",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدًا",
        "answer": "a promise",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "waʿdan",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَعِيدِ",
        "answer": "the warnings",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "l-waʿīdi",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "yattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلتَّقْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) for the righteous[ness]",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "lilttaqwā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَوَكَّأُ",
        "answer": "I lean",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "atawakka-u",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَوَلَّىٰ",
        "answer": "and turns away",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "watawallā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَوَلَّىٰ",
        "answer": "Then went away",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "fatawallā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنِيَا",
        "answer": "slacken",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taniyā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبَسًا",
        "answer": "dry",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yabasan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَكَ",
        "answer": "your hand",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "yadaka",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your hands",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "aydiyakum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "(is) before them",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسِّرْ",
        "answer": "And ease",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wayassir",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمِّ",
        "answer": "the river",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-yami",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمُّ",
        "answer": "the river",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-yamu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمِّ",
        "answer": "the sea",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-yami",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمِّ",
        "answer": "the sea",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-yami",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَيْمَنَ",
        "answer": "the right",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-aymana",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَمِينِكَ",
        "answer": "in your right hand",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "biyamīnika",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمِينِكَ",
        "answer": "your right hand",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yamīnika",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمُ",
        "answer": "(is on the) day",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "yawmu",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a day",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "yawman",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "today",
        "pcklId": "374",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "375",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "376",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "377",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "today",
        "pcklId": "378",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "20",
        "ayah": "126"
    }
]; 
export default words;